servicenow.com 2017-11-21

# Privacy Statement | IT Service Management Software, SaaS | ServiceNow

**Effective as of May 19, 2017**

##  Purpose 

ServiceNow, Inc., including its subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively, "ServiceNow", "we" or "us") respects the privacy of its customers, business partners, and visitors to its Website (as defined below). The ServiceNow Privacy Statement (the "Privacy Statement") describes the information that we collect, how we obtain the information, and how we may use or disclose that information. This Privacy Statement also describes the measures we take to protect the security of the information and how individuals can contact us about our privacy practices.

##  Scope 

This Privacy Statement only covers our privacy practices with respect to the collection, use, and disclosure of information obtained: (i) through the ServiceNow websites at www.servicenow.com, wiki.servicenow.com, community.servicenow.com, it3dot0.com and it3‑0.com (collectively, our "Website"); (ii) in connection with the use of applications downloaded to a User’s mobile device (“Mobile Applications”); and (iii) in connection with the use of our hosted software applications (the "Subscription Service") and related support services ("Support Services"), as well as expert services, including professional services, training and certification (the "Expert Services") that we provide to Customers. In this Privacy Statement, the Subscription Service, Support Services and the Expert Services are collectively referred to as the "Service." 

For the purposes of this Privacy Statement:

"Customer" means any entity that purchases the Service.  
"Customer Data" means the electronic data uploaded into the Subscription Service by or for Customer or its Users.  
"Visitor" means a visitor of the Website.

_"User_ ” means an individual authorized by Customer to access and use the Subscription Service.

##  Website 

**How We Obtain Information**    
As further described below, we collect several types of information from and about our Visitors. 

_Information you provide to us_

  * When filling out forms on our Website we collect personal information, including without limitation, name, mailing address, email address and telephone number.
  * When you post material to our Website, participate in bulletin boards, chat rooms, blogs, comment threads, forums or other interactive features of our Website, register, or request further information or services from us. 
  * When you register to use a demo or developer instance of the Subscription Service.
  * When you enter a contest or promotion we sponsor.
  * When you report a problem with our Website.
  * When you contact us.
  * When you complete our surveys.
  * Other information you may submit to us related to your use of our Website.

_Information from third parties_    
ServiceNow may collect and use information we receive from third parties in connection with your use of the Website.  For instance, ServiceNow uses a third party for reporting and analytics to measure the effectiveness of our Website and marketing efforts, and to identify areas for improvement. 

_Information we collect as you navigate through the Website_    
As you navigate through the Website, we may also collect details about your visits to our Website including, but not limited to, your IP address, usage patterns, traffic data, location data, logs and other communication data and the resources that you access, as well as information about your computer and internet connection, including your operating system and browser type. 

**_Cookies and Other Forms of Automated Collection_**    
We use “cookies” to help us improve our Website. A cookie is a small file stored on the hard drive of your computer. We may use cookies to obtain information about your general Internet usage and to: 

  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
  * Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website.
  * Speed up your searches.
  * Authenticate your access to various areas of our Website.
  * Recognize you when you return to our Website.
  * Track when you respond to surveys.

ServiceNow’s third parties may use JavaScript to collect IP addresses from our Visitors and our hosting provider may also collect server logs. Information gathered through these automated means may be associated with the personal information you previously submitted on our Website.

For detailed information regarding our use cookies, please see our [Cookies Policy](http://www.servicenow.com/cookie-policy.html).

**How We Use Information Collected**    
We may use information that we collect about Visitors for the following purposes:

  * To present our Website and their contents in a suitable and effective manner for you and for your computer.
  * To diagnose and resolve technical problems with our Website.
  * To improve our Website.
  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us.
  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including without limitation, our Website Terms of Use.
  * To notify you about changes to our Website or obtain any required consent.
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Website, when you choose to do so.
  * For industry analysis, benchmarking, analytics, marketing, and other business purposes. 
  * To track your browsing behavior, such as the pages you visited over time.

If you ask us to contact you about goods and services that may be of interest to you, we may use your personal information or permit selected third parties to use your personal information to provide you with such services. Visitors may withdraw consent at a later time by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link located in the emails sent by ServiceNow. For more information, see Communication Preferences and Choices below. 

**How We Share Information Collected**    
We may disclose personal information that you provide to us via this Website, to the following third parties:

  * Our subsidiaries and affiliates (including those located outside the European Economic Area and Switzerland).
  * Contractors, business partners and service providers we use to support our business or who provide services on our behalf.
  * In the event of merger, acquisition, or any form of sale or transfer of some or all of our assets (including in the event of a reorganization, dissolution or liquidation), in which case personal information held by us about our Visitors will be among the assets transferred to the buyer or acquirer.

We may also disclose your personal information to third parties to:

  * Comply with any court order or other legal obligation.
  * Enforce or apply our Website Terms of Use or terms of any other agreement.
  * Protect the rights, property, or safety of ServiceNow or others.

We do not sell, rent or trade information collected through the Website with third parties for their promotional purposes. 

**Public Forums and Blogs**    
Your User Contributions (as defined in the [Website Terms of Use](http://www.servicenow.com/terms-of-use.html)) are posted on and transmitted to other users of the Website at your own risk. Please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of your User Contributions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other Website users. Proper access and use of information provided on the Website, including User Contributions, is governed by our Website Terms of Use and known or suspected violations should be reported to our Privacy Officer via e‑mail at [privacy@servicenow.com](mailto:privacy@servicenow.com). 

**International Transfer of Data**    
ServiceNow may store and process any information collected in connection with the Website in any country where we have facilities or in which we engage service providers. A list of ServiceNow’s global offices is available [here](http://www.servicenow.com/contact-us.html). By using our Website, you consent to the collection, storage, transfer and processing of information outside of your country of residence, including in the United States.

**Communication Preferences and Choices**    
We provide certain choices regarding the information Visitors provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information when using our Website. If you do not wish to have your e‑mail address used for promotional purposes by ServiceNow, you may withdraw consent at a later time by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link located in the emails sent by ServiceNow. 

**_Cookies_**    
Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website. You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. You may also set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, if you do so, please note that some parts of our Website may then be inaccessible or function improperly.

**_Do Not Track_**    
While ServiceNow attempts to honor do not track (“DNT”) instructions we receive from a Visitor’s browser, we cannot guarantee that ServiceNow will always respond to such signals, in part, because of the lack of common industry standard for DNT technology. We continue to monitor developments in DNT technology and stay apprised of DNT industry standards as they evolve.

**_Choice_**    
You should review this Privacy Statement carefully, because if you do not agree with our practices, your ultimate choice is not to use the Website. Remember, by using any part of our Website, you accept and agree to our privacy practices. 

**Accessing and Correcting Your Personal Information**    
You may send us an e‑mail at [privacy@servicenow.com](mailto:privacy@servicenow.com) to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us in connection with the Website. We will use reasonable efforts to respond to such requests for correction or updates to personal information.

##  Services 

**How We Obtain Information**    
As described below, we collect several types of information from about our Customers, including:

  * General information, including a Customer’s company name and address, credit card information, and the Customer’s representative’s contact information (“General Information”) for billing and contracting purposes.
  * Information and correspondence our Customers and Users submit to us in connection with Expert Services or other requests related to our Service.
  * Information we receive from our business partners in connection with our Customers and Users use of the Service or in connection with services provided by our business partners on their behalf, including configuration of the Subscription Service.
  * Quantitative data derived from our Customers and Users use of the Subscription Service, for example and without limitation, the number of active roles within a Customer’s instance.  All data collected, used, and disclosed will be in aggregate form only and will not identify Customer or its Users.
  * Server logs in support of the Subscription Service.

**_Cookies_**    
When you use the Subscription Service, we use cookies to:

  * Track session state in the Subscription Service.
  * Route a browser request to a specific node when multiple nodes are assigned;
  * Authenticate your access to the Subscription Service.
  * Recognize you when you return to the Subscription Service.

Cookies must be enabled in order to use the Subscription Service. A User may however, refuse to accept the “remember me” cookie, which will then require a User to provide their username and password to log into the Subscription Service.

**How We Share Information Collected**    
We may disclose personal information that our Customers and Users provide to our Service, to the following third parties:

  * Our subsidiaries and affiliates (including those located outside the European Economic Area and Switzerland).
  * Contractors, business partners and service providers we use to support our Service and business partners who provide services on behalf of our Customers.
  * In the event of merger, acquisition, or any form of sale or transfer of some or all of our assets (including in the event of a reorganization, dissolution or liquidation), in which case personal information held by us about our Customers will be among the assets transferred to the buyer or acquirer.

We may also disclose your personal information to third parties to:

  * Comply with any court order or other legal obligation.
  * Enforce or apply the terms of the definitive agreement between Customer and ServiceNow pursuant to which the Customer purchased access to the Subscription Service (the “Customer Agreement”).
  * Protect the rights, property, or safety of ServiceNow, our Customers, Users or others.

We do not share, sell, rent or trade information collected through the Service with third parties for their promotional purposes.

**Customer Data**    
We may use Customer Data to provide the Service, including updating and maintaining the Subscription Service and providing Support and Expert Services. Notwithstanding anything else to the contrary in this Privacy Statement, we will not use, disclose, review, share, distribute, transfer or reference any Customer Data except as permitted in the Customer Agreement or as required by law.

**Communication Preferences and Choices and Accessing and Correcting Your Personal Information**    
Since each Customer is in control of what information, including any personal information, it collects from its Users, how that information is used and disclosed, and how that information can be changed, Users of the Subscription Service must contact the applicable Customer administrator with any inquiries about how the Customer uses and discloses personal information and how to access or correct personal information contained in Customer Data.

To access or correct any personal information Customer has provided as part of the General Information, the Customer should contact their account representative.  

**Mobile Applications**   
Without limiting the generality of this Policy, in addition to the information collected through the Website and the Service, ServiceNow may obtain additional information through Mobile Applications that Customer or their Users download to their mobile devices (“Devices”).  Mobile Applications provided by ServiceNow may obtain or collect information from Users’ Devices in connection with the Service and are designed to interoperate with the Subscription Service; for instance, to provide a User with access to information within the Subscription Service or to provide information from a User’s Device to the Subscription Service.

Mobile Applications may access the geographic location of a User’s Device.  Mobile Applications may also provide ServiceNow with information related to Users’ use of the Mobile Applications, including information regarding Users’ Devices and OS identification, login credentials, language and time zone.  Mobile Applications may also collect information regarding Users’ interaction with Mobile Applications, which ServiceNow may use to provide and improve the Mobile Application services.

Information accessed or obtained by the Mobile Application on a User’s Device may be accessible to the Customer and its organization, depending on the intended functionality of the Mobile Application.

Customer and its Users may configure Mobile Applications affecting the information collected or accessed on a User’s Device. 

In addition to Mobile Applications provided by ServiceNow, third party Mobile Applications may be made available for download to Users’ Devices.  The collection and use of information through third‑party Mobile Applications (if any) is governed by the applicable privacy notices of such third parties.

Contractual terms related to a particular Mobile Application may be found in the End User License Agreement or relevant terms of service for that application.

##  General 

**Transfers of Personal Data**   
ServiceNow, Inc. complies with the EU‑U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss – U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal information transferred from the European Economic Area and Switzerland to the United States. You can view a description of how we comply with the Privacy Shield Principles in our Privacy Shield Policy.  To learn more about the Privacy Shield Framework and the scope of ServiceNow’s participation, please visit the Department of Commerce’s website, located [here](https://www.privacyshield.gov/welcome).

**Security Statement**   
ServiceNow maintains reasonable and appropriate measures to protect the personal information obtained through the Website and in connection with the Service and Mobile Applications from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.

**Third Party Websites and Applications**    
This Website may link to websites that are not owned or controlled by ServiceNow. As such, this Privacy Statement does not apply to information collected on any third‑party site or by any third‑party application that may link to or be accessible from the Website. In addition, Customers and other third parties, including our business partners and consultants, may develop applications (including Mobile Applications) or provide services to you or other third parties using our Service. This Privacy Statement does not apply to information collected by Customers, our business partners and other third parties or third‑party applications (including Mobile Applications) or services, even if this information is collected using our Website or Service. This Privacy Statement also does not cover the use or disclosure of any information stored in the Subscription Service when hosted by the Customer. 

**Changes to Our Privacy Statement**    
ServiceNow reserves the right to update or change this Privacy Statement from time to time. If we make material changes to this Privacy Statement, we will notify you through an appropriate online notice (and obtain your consent where required by applicable law). Your continued use of the Website or Service is deemed to be acceptance of any updates or changes we make to this Privacy Statement and as such, we ask that you review the Privacy Statement periodically for any updates or changes that we may have made.

**Contact Information**    
To ask questions or comment about this Privacy Statement and our privacy practices or if you need to update, change or remove your information, contact us at: [privacy@servicenow.com](mailto:privacy@servicenow.com).

or

ServiceNow, Inc.  
Attn: Privacy  
2225 Lawson Lane  
Santa Clara, CA 95054

All other feedback, comments, requests for technical support and other communications relating to the Website should be directed to: [marketing@servicenow.com](mailto:marketing@servicenow.com).

This website is operated by ServiceNow, Inc., a Delaware corporation located at 2225 Lawson Lane, Santa Clara, CA 95054.
